[
  [
    "Antofagasta agreed to invest $4.4 billion to expand its Centinela copper mine in Chile.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          41,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          81,
          86,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Trading was paused due to a volatility halt after the stock dropped 20%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          28,
          43,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Shares of Snap plummeted 14% after the social media firm warned that ad revenue would be flat in Q4.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          14,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          25,
          28,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          97,
          99,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bank of England is concerned that sticky services inflation will prevent early rate cuts in 2026.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          19,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          45,
          63,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          96,
          100,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Australian miner BHP Group offered $39 billion to acquire Anglo American to secure access to its copper mines.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          17,
          26,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          35,
          46,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          58,
          72,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon will share his annual shareholder letter on Wednesday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          18,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          19,
          30,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          75,
          84,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Disney (DIS) defeated activist investors in a proxy battle regarding board seats at the annual shareholder meeting.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          11,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Berkshire Hathaway Vice Chairman Charlie Munger passed away at the age of 99 on Tuesday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          19,
          32,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          33,
          47,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          80,
          87,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau banned Unicoin from operating in the US after it falsely claimed its tokens were backed by real estate assets.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          48,
          55,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Trading was paused due to a volatility halt after the stock dropped 20%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          28,
          43,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Turkish Lira hit a record low of 32.6 against the dollar, pressuring the central bank to hike rates to 50%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          16,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          37,
          41,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          107,
          110,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A stock split for Nvidia (NVDA) could boost retail participation.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          2,
          13,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          18,
          24,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          26,
          30,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Philly Fed Index came in below expectations.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          20,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The de-listing of Didi from the NYSE was completed today.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          14,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          18,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "German chemical giant BASF is cutting 2,600 jobs to save €500 million annually.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          22,
          26,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          43,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          57,
          69,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The unemployment rate ticked up to 3.9% in February, reaching its highest level in two years.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          35,
          39,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          43,
          51,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "UBS raised its target for Netflix to $700, praising the success of its ad-supported tier.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          26,
          33,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          37,
          41,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Supreme Court declined to hear the appeal regarding the patent dispute between Novo Nordisk and Dr. Reddy's Laboratories over the weight-loss drug Wegovy.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          83,
          95,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          100,
          124,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          151,
          157,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Super Micro Computer (SMCI) joined the S&P 500 index following its rally.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          22,
          26,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          39,
          46,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Elliott Management launched a tender offer for Crown Castle.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          30,
          42,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          59,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Bristol Myers Squibb agreed to buy neuroscience drugmaker Karuna Therapeutics for $14 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          58,
          77,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          82,
          93,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The board of directors at Wells Fargo has named Charlie Scharf as the new CEO and President, effective immediately.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          26,
          37,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          48,
          62,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          74,
          77,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          82,
          91,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Fed Chair Powell discussed the PCE deflator during his testimony.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          16,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          31,
          43,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A surprise drop in Retail Sales sparked recession fears.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          19,
          31,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Producer Price Index rose 0.6% in February, driven by higher fuel and food costs.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          24,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          30,
          34,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          38,
          46,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Analysts at Goldman Sachs have downgraded Rio Tinto to 'Neutral', citing a 10% drop in iron ore prices.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          12,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          42,
          51,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          78,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Goldman Sachs announced that David Solomon has been appointed as Chairman of the board, in addition to his current duties as CEO.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          42,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          65,
          73,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          125,
          128,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Bridgewater Associates named Nir Bar Dea as its sole CEO following a leadership restructuring.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          40,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          53,
          56,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Tim Cook, CEO of Apple, unveiled the new Vision Pro headset at the company's Worldwide Developers Conference.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          10,
          13,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          17,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "US GDP grew at an annualized rate of 1.6% in Q1, marking a significant slowdown from the previous quarter.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          37,
          41,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          45,
          47,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Upcoming data on initial jobless claims and continuing claims will guide the Fed.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          17,
          39,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          44,
          61,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Elliott Management launched a tender offer for Crown Castle.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          30,
          42,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          59,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Institute for Supply Management services index dipped to 51.4 in March, driven by lower new orders.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          61,
          65,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          69,
          74,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Shein filed confidential papers for a US IPO.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          44,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The hostile takeover bid for U.S. Steel (X) by Nippon Steel sparked political debate.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          20,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          29,
          39,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          42,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          47,
          59,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Wheat prices jumped 4% after Russia targeted grain infrastructure in the Odesa port region.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          20,
          22,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          29,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          73,
          78,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The rebalancing of the Nasdaq 100 index forced funds to sell big tech.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          15,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Series B round for Perplexity AI attracted Nvidia (NVDA) as an investor.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          18,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          23,
          36,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          53,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          55,
          59,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Truist Financial agreed to sell its insurance brokerage unit to an investor group for $15.5 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          16,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          99,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Vietnam's VinFast is delaying its $4 billion factory construction in North Carolina until 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          34,
          44,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          69,
          83,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          90,
          94,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The United Auto Workers union secured a 25% wage hike over four years after the strike against Ford.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          23,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          40,
          43,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          95,
          99,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz led a $100 million Series B funding round for crypto startup EigenLayer.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          21,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          59,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          60,
          76,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          102,
          112,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Dell (DELL) surged on AI server demand, joining the AI rally.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          6,
          10,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          52,
          60,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Berkshire Hathaway acquired a massive stake in Chubb.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          43,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          52,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "GameStop announced a stock split to make shares more affordable.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          32,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "In an interview with Bloomberg on Tuesday, Larry Fink, the CEO of BlackRock, discussed the future of sustainable investing.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          34,
          41,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          43,
          53,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          59,
          62,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          66,
          75,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Capital One announced it would acquire Discover Financial in a $35.3 billion all-stock deal.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          39,
          57,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          63,
          76,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Pfizer completed its $43 billion acquisition of cancer drugmaker Seagen on December 14.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          32,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          65,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          86,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Walmart warned that consumer spending is softening, predicting a flat same-store sales growth for Q4 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          98,
          105,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "SoftBank (9984.T) is targeting a listing for its chip unit Arm (ARM).",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          10,
          16,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          33,
          40,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          59,
          62,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          64,
          67,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Thierry Breton, the EU internal market commissioner, demanded that TikTok spare no effort to protect teenagers.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          20,
          51,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          67,
          73,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "SpaceX insiders claim the company's valuation has now topped $180 billion following the secondary sale.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          61,
          73,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "LVMH saw organic revenue growth slow to 9% in Q3 as luxury demand cooled in Europe.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          40,
          42,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          46,
          48,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          76,
          82,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Taiwan Semiconductor confirmed that revenue for October jumped 34.8% thanks to booming AI chip demand.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          48,
          55,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          63,
          68,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Shareholders of Tesla are suing the board, claiming that excessive compensation packages diluted their equity by 3% in 2024.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          16,
          21,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          113,
          115,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          119,
          123,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Alphabet shares slid 4% after the company reported Q3 ad revenue of $59.6 billion, missing estimates.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          23,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          51,
          53,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          68,
          81,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Johnson & Johnson completed the spinoff of its consumer health unit, Kenvue, on August 23.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          69,
          75,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          80,
          89,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Petrobras shares plunged 6% after the Brazilian government hinted at changing the dividend policy on May 14.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          25,
          27,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          101,
          107,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Disney (DIS) won the proxy vote, avoiding a board shakeup.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          11,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          50,
          57,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Post-market trading saw Coinbase jump 6% after Bitcoin reclaimed the $65,000 level.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          24,
          32,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          40,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          54,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          69,
          76,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Inflation in Egypt soared to 35.7% in February following the central bank's decision to float the pound.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          13,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          34,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          38,
          46,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "In a blow to Bayer, a jury in Philadelphia awarded $2.25 billion to a plaintiff who claimed the weedkiller Roundup caused his cancer.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          13,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          30,
          42,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          51,
          64,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Caterpillar stock rose 5% as the industrial giant reported record free cash flow of $3 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          23,
          25,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          84,
          94,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Walmart is buying smart TV maker Vizio for $2.3 billion to boost its ad business.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          33,
          38,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          43,
          55,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Japan's Nikkei 225 index crossed the 40,000 mark for the first time in history on Monday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          18,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          37,
          43,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          82,
          88,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Paramount Global has entered exclusive merger talks with Skydance Media, sources told CNBC.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          16,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          57,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          90,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Broadcom finally closed its $69 billion acquisition of VMware on Wednesday after receiving regulatory clearance.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          28,
          39,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          55,
          61,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          65,
          74,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Germany's industrial output dropped 0.4% in January, raising fears of a protracted downturn.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          40,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          44,
          51,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Reserve Bank of Australia left the cash rate target at 4.35% on Tuesday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          29,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          59,
          64,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          68,
          75,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Despite the plea, Judge Leonie Brinkema ruled that Google holds two illegal monopolies in the search market.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          18,
          39,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          51,
          57,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Mary Barra, CEO of General Motors, stated that the company plans to invest $35 billion in electric and autonomous vehicles through 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          12,
          15,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          19,
          33,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          86,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          131,
          135,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm terminated its bid to acquire Autotalks citing regulatory hurdles.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          39,
          48,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "UK inflation dropped to 3.4% in February, the lowest level in two and a half years.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          2,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          24,
          28,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          32,
          40,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Reddit launched its IPO on Thursday, valuing the social media platform at $6.4 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          35,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          74,
          86,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "ConocoPhillips agreed to buy Marathon Oil in a $22.5 billion all-stock transaction.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          41,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          60,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The latest JOLTS job openings data signaled a cooling labor market.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          11,
          29,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Initial jobless claims rose to 221,000 for the week ending March 30, the highest level in two months.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          31,
          38,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          59,
          67,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Pending home sales rebounded 1.6% in February despite mortgage rates remaining near 7%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          29,
          33,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          37,
          45,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          84,
          86,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Kristalina Georgieva, Managing Director of the IMF, approved a $1.1 billion disbursement to Pakistan.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          22,
          39,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          47,
          50,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          63,
          75,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          92,
          100,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Bank of America reiterated its 'Buy' rating on Apple ahead of the September product launch event.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          15,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          52,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          66,
          75,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The yield on the 10-year Treasury note surged to 4.7% following the hot inflation report.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          17,
          38,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          49,
          53,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Labor Force Participation Rate is a key metric alongside the Unemployment Rate.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          34,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          65,
          82,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Despite a 40% year-over-year revenue increase, Nvidia shares remained flat on Tuesday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          13,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          53,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          78,
          85,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Federal prosecutors seized $198 million in assets from PGI Global, labeling the operation a 'classic Ponzi scheme' targeting retail crypto investors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          27,
          39,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          55,
          65,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "China's Caixin Services PMI remained in expansion territory.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          27,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "T-Mobile announced a $4.4 billion deal to acquire US Cellular's wireless operations.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          33,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          50,
          61,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Look for the ISM Manufacturing PMI and Services PMI to define the trend.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          13,
          34,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          39,
          51,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The PCE Deflator is the Fed's favorite inflation gauge.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          16,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Inflation as measured by the CPI rose 3.2% year-over-year in February, slightly higher than the 3.1% forecast.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          38,
          42,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          61,
          69,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          96,
          100,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The European Central Bank is closely monitoring the Eurozone HICP inflation rate, which held steady at 2.6%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          80,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          103,
          107,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The trade deficit widened to $68.9 billion in February as imports outpaced exports.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          29,
          42,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          46,
          54,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Starbucks reported that global comparable store sales rose 8%, driven by a 5% increase in average ticket size.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          59,
          61,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          75,
          77,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Moody's downgraded the credit outlook for New York Community Bancorp to 'Negative' on Friday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          42,
          68,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          92,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The spread between the 2-year Treasury yield and the 10-year Treasury yield inverted further.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          23,
          44,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          53,
          75,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Durable Goods Orders rebounded thanks to aircraft demand.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Producer Prices (PPI) came in hotter than expected compared to Consumer Prices (CPI).",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          63,
          84,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "JPMorgan sees Amazon as a 'Top Pick' for 2026, forecasting 15% upside from current levels.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          14,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          45,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          59,
          62,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Visa announced that Ryan McInerney would become CEO on February 1, 2023, succeeding Al Kelly.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          20,
          34,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          48,
          51,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          55,
          71,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          84,
          92,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Satya Nadella, Chairman and CEO of Microsoft, emphasized the importance of cloud computing in the company's earnings call.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          15,
          23,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          28,
          31,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          35,
          44,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A federal judge in Texas struck down the National Labor Relations Board's new rule on joint-employer status, calling it 'overly broad'.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          19,
          24,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Watch the ADP Employment Change figures closely before the official jobs report.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          31,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Apollo Global Management co-founder Marc Rowan has taken over as CEO after the departure of Leon Black.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          24,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          46,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          65,
          68,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          92,
          102,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "CFRA raised its opinion on General Motors to 'Buy' after the company announced a $10 billion buyback.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          41,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          81,
          92,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Stripe is preparing for a direct listing IPO rather than a traditional initial public offering.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          44,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          71,
          94,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Universal Music Group sued AI startup Anthropic for $75 million, claiming widespread copyright infringement in its training data.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          47,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          63,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Department of Justice is seeking more than $4 billion in penalties from Binance.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          57,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          76,
          83,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bank of Japan intervened in the currency market after the yen weakened to 160 against the dollar on Monday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          78,
          81,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          104,
          110,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The latest JOLTS job openings data signaled a cooling labor market.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          11,
          29,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Goldman Sachs (GS) acted as the lead advisor on the $53 billion merger between Chevron and Hess.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          17,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          52,
          63,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          64,
          70,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          79,
          86,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          91,
          95,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Venture capital funding in the fintech sector plummeted 35% in 2024 compared to the previous year.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          56,
          59,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          63,
          67,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Chevron announced a definitive agreement to acquire Hess in an all-stock transaction valued at $53 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          56,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          95,
          106,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Traders reacted negatively to the hot Core CPI print this morning.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          38,
          46,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "On September 5, the European Commission designated Booking.com as a 'gatekeeper' under the Digital Markets Act, forcing it to comply with stricter interoperability rules.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          14,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          20,
          39,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          51,
          62,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "German ZEW Economic Sentiment improved slightly in November.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          29,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Led by CEO Satya Nadella, Microsoft has committed $2.9 billion to build data centers in Japan.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          7,
          10,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          11,
          24,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          26,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          50,
          62,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          88,
          93,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Case-Shiller Home Price Index showed a 5% year-over-year increase.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          33,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "SoftBank is considering a block sale of its Alibaba shares.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          26,
          36,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "ExxonMobil delivered a massive $9.1 billion profit for Q3 2025, fueled by rising crude prices.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          31,
          43,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          55,
          62,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Biopharma firm FibroGen agreed to pay $1.25 million to settle charges that it misled investors about the safety data of its anemia drug, Roxadustat.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          15,
          23,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          51,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          137,
          147,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Arm Holdings issued bullish guidance for fiscal 2026, expecting revenue to top $3 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          52,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          79,
          89,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "RBC Capital raised its target for Shopify to $95, expecting strong GMV growth in the holiday season.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          34,
          41,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          45,
          48,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Average hourly earnings increased 0.2% month-over-month, signaling that wage pressures are easing.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          34,
          38,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Oracle (ORCL) announced a debt offering to finance its data center expansion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          12,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          26,
          39,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Alibaba scrapped plans to spin off its cloud unit, causing the stock to drop 10% on Thursday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          77,
          80,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          84,
          92,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Meta (META) declared a dividend, a rare financial event for a tech giant.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          6,
          10,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          40,
          55,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "On Thursday, Netflix announced it added 5.9 million net new subscribers in the third quarter.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          11,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          13,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          40,
          51,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Swiss National Bank surprised markets with a rate cut to 1.5% to curb the franc's strength.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          23,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          61,
          65,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "TotalEnergies signed a deal to develop a $10 billion offshore oil project in Suriname.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          41,
          52,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          77,
          85,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Crude oil futures dipped below $70 per barrel for the first time since December 2023 due to weak demand from China.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          31,
          34,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          71,
          84,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          109,
          114,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "SoftBank is considering a block sale of its Alibaba shares.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          26,
          36,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Inflation expectations have anchored near 3%, according to the Michigan Survey.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          22,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          63,
          78,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Carlyle Group appointed Harvey Schwartz, a former Goldman Sachs executive, as its new CEO.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          24,
          39,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          50,
          63,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          89,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Guggenheim lowered its price target for Pfizer to $28, reflecting weak sales of its Covid portfolio.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          40,
          46,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          50,
          53,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "China's Caixin Services PMI remained in expansion territory.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          27,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The EPA announced a settlement with Norfolk Southern, requiring the rail giant to pay $310 million for the environmental cleanup.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          52,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          98,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Reddit officially filed for an IPO under the ticker symbol $RDDT, targeting a valuation of over $6 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          31,
          34,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          59,
          64,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          96,
          106,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Target shares surged 17% after the retailer reported much better-than-feared margins for Q3.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          24,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          89,
          91,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Housing starts plunged 14.7% in March, the biggest drop since the pandemic began.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          23,
          28,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          32,
          37,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bureau of Economic Analysis reported that real gross domestic product increased at an annual rate of 3.2% in Q4 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          31,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          46,
          73,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          105,
          109,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          113,
          120,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The UK Competition and Markets Authority blocked the acquisition of Activision by Microsoft before reversing its decision on October 13.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          68,
          78,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          82,
          91,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          125,
          135,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Traders are awaiting the non-farm payrolls report on Friday to gauge the health of the labor market.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          25,
          42,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          53,
          59,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Inflation in the Eurozone cooled to 2.4% in March, defying expectations of a sticky 2.6%.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          17,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          40,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          44,
          49,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          84,
          88,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A surprise drop in Retail Sales sparked recession fears.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          19,
          31,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Intel provided a gloomy forecast for Q1 2026, expecting revenue between $12.2 billion and $13.2 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          37,
          44,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          72,
          85,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          90,
          103,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Copper futures on the LME surged to $9,000 per tonne on Friday amid supply disruptions in Panama.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          22,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          42,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          56,
          62,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          90,
          96,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Mastercard CEO Michael Miebach discussed the company's strategy for digital payments and cryptocurrency.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          11,
          14,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          15,
          30,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Sundar Pichai, CEO of Alphabet and Google, announced a new AI research hub in Paris.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          15,
          18,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          22,
          30,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          35,
          41,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          59,
          61,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          78,
          83,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "HSBC downgraded Nike to 'Hold', warning of increasing competition from On Running and Hoka.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          16,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          71,
          81,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          90,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Weekly jobless claims fell to 210,000, showing resilience.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "UBS has re-appointed Sergio Ermotti as Group Chief Executive Officer to lead the integration of Credit Suisse.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          35,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          39,
          68,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          96,
          109,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "GameStop announced a stock split to make shares more affordable.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          32,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Traders are watching the VIX volatility index as put/call ratios hit extremes.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          25,
          28,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          49,
          64,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The SEC charged Ryan Squillante, a former Head of Equity Trading, with insider trading that allegedly generated $216,000 in illicit profits.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          16,
          31,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          42,
          64,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          112,
          120,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Empire State Manufacturing Index plummeted to -14.5.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          36,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Former Bank of England governor Mark Carney has joined Brookfield Asset Management as Vice Chair and Head of Transition Investing.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          7,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          32,
          43,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          55,
          82,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          86,
          96,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          101,
          129,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "China's exports grew, but imports shrank, widening the trade surplus.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          15,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          26,
          33,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Evergrande's liquidation order has sent shockwaves through the property sector, wiping out $300 billion in value.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          91,
          103,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Hank Paulson has joined the board of directors at TPG Capital.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          7,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          31,
          43,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          81,
          92,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala, the Director-General of the WTO, warned that fragmentation could cost the global economy 5% of GDP.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          19,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          25,
          41,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          49,
          52,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          110,
          112,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Oppenheimer analyst Rick Schafer raised his target on NXP Semiconductors to $280.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          20,
          32,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          54,
          72,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          76,
          80,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Broadcom (AVGO) shares rose after completing the spinoff of its end-user computing unit.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          10,
          14,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          49,
          56,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "U.S. crude oil inventories rose by 3 million barrels, pressuring prices.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          26,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "On Wednesday, BYD overtook Tesla as the top-selling EV brand in Singapore.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          14,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          32,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          64,
          73,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "GameStop (GME) and AMC (AMC) saw a resurgence in meme stock activity.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          10,
          13,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          19,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          24,
          27,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Wedbush analyst Dan Ives maintained an 'Outperform' rating on Tesla with a $300 price target.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          16,
          24,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          62,
          67,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          79,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Unilever announced it would spin off its ice cream division, which includes Ben & Jerry's, by the end of 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          76,
          89,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          105,
          109,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Investors are waiting for the flash PMI readings from Europe.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          30,
          39,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Federal Reserve pays close attention to the Employment Cost Index to watch for wage-push inflation.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          19,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          48,
          69,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Amazon defeated a proposed class action claiming it inflated the prices of e-books in collusion with major publishers.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Thoma Bravo completed the take-private acquisition of Everbridge for $1.5 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          54,
          64,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          69,
          81,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The merger between Kroger and Albertsons, valued at roughly $24.6 billion, faces stiff antitrust scrutiny.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          19,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          30,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          60,
          73,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Empire State Manufacturing Index plummeted to -14.5.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          36,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The South African Reserve Bank kept its main lending rate at 8.25%, citing persistent food inflation.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          30,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          61,
          66,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "China's internet watchdog imposed a $1.2 billion fine on ride-hailing giant Didi Global for violating data security laws.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          48,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          76,
          87,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Shares of Tesla (TSLA) slid 4% after the company announced a delay in its upcoming robotaxi unveiling.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          15,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          17,
          21,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          28,
          30,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Codelco, the world's largest copper producer, reported a production slump to 1.32 million tonnes in 2023.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          77,
          96,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          100,
          104,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Russian gas giant Gazprom reported a net loss of $6.9 billion for 2023, its first annual loss in decades.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          18,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          49,
          61,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          66,
          70,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Nippon Steel clinched a deal to buy US Steel for $14.9 billion, creating a global steel giant.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          44,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          49,
          62,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "On Wednesday, OpenAI confirmed that Sam Altman would return as CEO.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          14,
          20,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          46,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          63,
          66,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Amazon ($AMZN) abandoned its planned $1.4 billion acquisition of iRobot due to EU opposition.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          13,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          37,
          49,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          50,
          61,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          65,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Salesforce (CRM) announced a definitive agreement for the acquisition of data management firm Informatica.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          12,
          15,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          58,
          69,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          94,
          105,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Lina Khan, the Chair of the FTC, vowed to appeal the decision, emphasizing that big tech monopolies stifle innovation.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          15,
          20,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          28,
          31,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Cybersecurity firm Rubrik filed for an IPO on the NYSE under the ticker $RBRK.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          19,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          39,
          42,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          50,
          54,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          72,
          77,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Rivian (RIVN) paused the construction of its Georgia plant to save cash.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          12,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Abu Dhabi's Adnoc formally approached Covestro with a takeover offer valued at €11 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          12,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          46,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          79,
          90,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "German ZEW Economic Sentiment improved slightly in November.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          29,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "U.S. crude oil inventories rose by 3 million barrels, pressuring prices.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          26,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Traders reacted negatively to the hot Core CPI print this morning.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          38,
          46,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "BBVA launched a hostile takeover bid for rival Spanish bank Sabadell valued at €12 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          60,
          68,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          79,
          90,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Investors are waiting for the flash PMI readings from Europe.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          30,
          39,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Disney faced a proxy battle from activist investors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          27,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Jane Fraser, the CEO of Citi, warned that persistence inflation could force the Fed to keep rates high through 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          17,
          20,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          24,
          28,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          80,
          83,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          111,
          115,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Palantir (PLTR) soared after securing a new government contract.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          10,
          14,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "On Monday, the Supreme Court of India rejected the plea by Vodafone Idea to recalculate its adjusted gross revenue dues.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          9,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          15,
          37,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          59,
          72,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "UK GDP contracted, pushing the FTSE 100 into negative territory.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          31,
          39,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Eurozone PMI and UK PMI diverged significantly this month.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          16,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          21,
          27,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The sudden rally in bond yields spooked equity investors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          11,
          16,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Citi opened a 'negative catalyst watch' on Intel, predicting a revenue miss in Q4 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          43,
          48,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          79,
          86,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Retail sales in the US were flat in April, missing the economist consensus of a 0.4% increase.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          20,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          41,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          80,
          84,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Global debt hit a record $313 trillion in 2024, according to the Institute of International Finance.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          25,
          38,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          42,
          46,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          65,
          99,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "UnitedHealth (UNH) fell after the cyberattack on its subsidiary.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          14,
          17,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          34,
          45,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Microsoft ($MSFT) completed its $69 billion merger with Activision Blizzard, ending a lengthy regulatory battle.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          11,
          16,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          32,
          43,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          44,
          50,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          56,
          75,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "KeyBanc maintained an 'Overweight' rating on CrowdStrike, citing strong cybersecurity spending trends.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          45,
          56,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Zurich Insurance posted a record operating profit of $3.7 billion, driven by strong underwriting.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          16,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          53,
          65,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The US economy added 275,000 jobs in November, smashing estimates of 190,000.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          28,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          37,
          45,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          69,
          76,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Mizuho analyst Vijay Rakesh believes Micron is well-positioned to benefit from the HBM3 shortage.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          27,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          37,
          43,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Nvidia (NVDA) overtook Alphabet (GOOGL) in market cap following a blowout earnings report.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          12,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          23,
          31,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          33,
          38,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The de-listing of Didi from the NYSE was completed today.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          14,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          18,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Consumer Price Index rose 0.4% in September, indicating that inflation remains persistent.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          24,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          30,
          34,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          38,
          47,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Vale admitted that iron ore output at its S11D mine was 5% below targets due to heavy rains in the Amazon.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          56,
          58,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          99,
          105,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Bernstein analyst Toni Sacconaghi questioned the valuation of Palantir, setting a price target of just $10.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          18,
          33,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          62,
          70,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          103,
          106,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The market entered a correction after falling 10% from highs.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          21,
          31,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Glencore is planning to spin off its coal business after acquiring a 77% stake in Teck Resources' steelmaking coal unit.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          69,
          72,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          82,
          96,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Morgan Stanley raised its price target on Nvidia to $1,200, citing accelerating demand for its H100 chips.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          42,
          48,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          58,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Visa (V) and Mastercard (MA) announced a settlement regarding swipe fees.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          6,
          7,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          13,
          23,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          25,
          27,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Meta COO Sheryl Sandberg stepped down from her role after 14 years at the company.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          5,
          8,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          9,
          24,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The correlation between $BTC-USD and $ETH-USD has decoupled from the Nasdaq 100.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          24,
          32,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          37,
          45,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          69,
          79,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Permira and Blackstone proposed a roughly €14 billion buyout of online classifieds group Adevinta.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          12,
          22,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          42,
          53,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          89,
          97,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Existing home sales rose, but pending home sales remained flat.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          19,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          30,
          48,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Effective January 1, Jane Fraser will assume the role of Chief Executive Officer at Citigroup, succeeding Michael Corbat.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          19,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          21,
          32,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          57,
          80,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          84,
          93,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          106,
          120,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "T-Mobile (TMUS) announced a $19 billion share buyback program.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          10,
          14,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          28,
          39,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          40,
          53,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Tesla 's Technoking, Elon Musk, indicated that the company might resume accepting Bitcoin for vehicle purchases.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          9,
          19,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          21,
          30,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          82,
          89,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Indonesia's ban on nickel ore exports has forced foreign investors to pour $15 billion into local smelters since 2020.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          75,
          86,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          113,
          117,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Analysts at Jefferies slashed their target for Lululemon to $350, warning of slowing apparel demand.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          12,
          21,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          56,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          60,
          64,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Adobe terminated its $20 billion merger with Figma due to pressure from the UK and EU regulators.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          21,
          32,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          45,
          50,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          76,
          78,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          83,
          85,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Durable Goods Orders rebounded thanks to aircraft demand.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          20,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The People's Bank of China injected 100 billion yuan into the banking system to maintain liquidity.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          26,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          52,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Series A funding for Mistral AI valued the company at €2 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          20,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          25,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Consumer confidence in the US fell to 104.7 in March, down from a revised 104.8 in the prior month.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          27,
          29,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          43,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          47,
          52,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          74,
          79,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Berkshire Hathaway acquired a massive stake in Chubb.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          18,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          43,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          52,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "OpenAI faces a new class-action lawsuit filed in California, alleging it scraped copyrighted material from New York Times without compensation.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          49,
          59,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          107,
          121,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "PayPal pointed to Alex Chriss as its new President and CEO, effective September 27, 2023.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          18,
          29,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          41,
          50,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          55,
          58,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          70,
          88,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A short squeeze sent shares of Carvana up 40% in one day.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          2,
          15,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          31,
          38,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Federal Reserve held interest rates steady at 5.25%-5.50% but signaled three rate cuts for 2026.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          19,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          50,
          61,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          95,
          99,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "As of Friday, the 10-year Treasury yield spiked to 4.5%, pressuring growth stocks.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          6,
          12,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          18,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          51,
          55,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Spot gold prices breached the $2,400 mark on April 12 as geopolitical tensions in the Middle East escalated.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          30,
          36,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          45,
          53,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Core PCE Price Index is preferred over the CPI for inflation tracking.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          24,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          47,
          50,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Goldman Sachs initiated coverage on Arm Holdings with a 'Buy' rating and a $85 price objective.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          48,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          78,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Consumer confidence dipped to 102.0, contrasting with strong retail sales data.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          19,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          61,
          73,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The acquisition of Ansys by Synopsys is the largest M&A deal this year.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          15,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          19,
          24,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          28,
          36,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          55,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bureau of Labor Statistics reported that productivity rose 3.2% in the first quarter of 2025.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          30,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          63,
          67,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          92,
          96,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Institute for Supply Management's Manufacturing PMI fell to 47.8% in February, indicating contraction.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          55,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          64,
          69,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          73,
          81,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Disney faced a proxy battle from activist investors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          27,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Bank of England voted 7-2 to keep the base rate at 5.25%, stating inflation remains 'sticky'.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          19,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          55,
          60,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A massive sell-off in tech stocks dragged the Nasdaq down.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          18,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "AMD forecasted AI chip sales of $2 billion for 2026, signaling a strong challenge to Nvidia.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          32,
          42,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          47,
          51,
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          85,
          91,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Irish Data Protection Commission slapped TikTok with a record €530 million fine for mishandling the data of teenagers.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          36,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          45,
          51,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          66,
          78,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Saudi Arabia announced it would extend its voluntary oil production cut of 1 million bpd through Q2.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          75,
          88,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          97,
          99,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Rubrik, a cloud data security firm backed by Microsoft, is planning an IPO to raise $750 million.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          45,
          54,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          84,
          96,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Lina Khan, Chair of the FTC, blocked the acquisition on grounds that it would harm competition.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          11,
          16,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          24,
          27,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The private placement raised $50 million for the biotech startup.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          21,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A short squeeze sent shares of Carvana up 40% in one day.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          2,
          15,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          31,
          38,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Philly Fed Index came in below expectations.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          20,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Liberty Media announced plans to split into two tracking stocks to unlock value in SiriusXM.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          83,
          91,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Watch the ADP Employment Change figures closely before the official jobs report.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          31,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Analysts were impressed by Palantir's 20% year-over-year growth in commercial revenue reported on Monday.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          27,
          35,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          38,
          41,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          98,
          104,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The private placement raised $50 million for the biotech startup.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          21,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Japan's Tankan Large Manufacturers Index improved in Q4.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          40,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "A massive sell-off in tech stocks dragged the Nasdaq down.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          18,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "IMF has appointed Gita Gopinath as its First Deputy Managing Director, the second-highest position at the fund.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          18,
          31,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          39,
          69,
          "ROLE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Home Depot struck a deal to buy SRS Distribution for $18.25 billion to expand its pro business.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          32,
          48,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          53,
          67,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "BlackRock intends to acquire Global Infrastructure Partners for roughly $12.5 billion in cash and stock.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          9,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          29,
          59,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          72,
          85,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Boeing narrowed its loss to $1.6 billion but lowered its delivery target for the 737 Max.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          28,
          40,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The liquidity injection by the central bank calmed the banking crisis.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          23,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The market entered a correction after falling 10% from highs.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          21,
          31,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "German Factory Orders dropped, weighing on the DAX index.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          47,
          50,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Uber posted its first-ever annual operating profit of $1.1 billion, marking a turning point for the ride-hailing giant.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          54,
          66,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "MicroStrategy (MSTR) bought more Bitcoin, acting as a proxy for the crypto asset.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          19,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Loop Capital upgraded Pinterest to 'Buy', arguing that ad monetization is improving faster than expected.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          22,
          31,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Needham raised its forecast for Uber, expecting gross bookings to grow 20% year-over-year.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          7,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          32,
          36,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          71,
          74,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Delta Air Lines sees record travel demand, projecting revenue of $14 billion for the holiday quarter ending December 31.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          15,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          65,
          76,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          108,
          119,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Crude Oil Inventories rose, pushing oil prices down.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Commodity Futures Trading Commission ordered Coinbase to pay a $6.5 million penalty for reporting false trading data.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          40,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          49,
          57,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          67,
          79,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Synopsys will acquire engineering software firm Ansys for $35 billion in a cash-and-stock deal.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          8,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          48,
          53,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          58,
          69,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Meta Platforms (META) declared its first-ever quarterly dividend of $0.50 per share.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          16,
          20,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          68,
          73,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The sudden rally in bond yields spooked equity investors.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          11,
          16,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The PCE Deflator is the Fed's favorite inflation gauge.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          16,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Smurfit Kappa agreed to merge with WestRock to create a packaging giant worth $20 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          13,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          35,
          43,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          78,
          89,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Housing starts and building permits both fell, signaling a construction slowdown.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          14,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          19,
          35,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Blackstone President Jon Gray said the firm sees significant opportunities in the real estate sector.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          11,
          20,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          21,
          29,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Mexico's state oil company Pemex received a $8 billion tax break to help manage its massive debt load.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          32,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          44,
          54,
          "MONEY"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "KKR co-founders Henry Kravis and George Roberts have stepped down as co-CEOs, handing the reins to Joe Bae and Scott Nuttall.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          16,
          28,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          33,
          47,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          99,
          106,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          111,
          124,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Zoom reported enterprise revenue of $660 million, up 7.5% year-over-year.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          36,
          48,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          53,
          57,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Exxon Mobil (XOM) completed its acquisition of Pioneer Natural Resources in an all-stock deal.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          11,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          13,
          16,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          32,
          43,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          47,
          72,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The merger between Kroger (KR) and Albertsons (ACI) faces antitrust roadblocks.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          10,
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          19,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          29,
          "TICKER"
        ],
        [
          35,
          45,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          47,
          50,
          "TICKER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Saudi Aramco CEO Amin Nasser said the energy transition is failing and demand for oil will continue rising.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          13,
          16,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          17,
          28,
          "PER"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The liquidity injection by the central bank calmed the banking crisis.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          23,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "US retail sales rebounded 0.6% in March, suggesting consumers remain resilient.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          3,
          15,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          26,
          30,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          34,
          39,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "GDP growth slowed, but industrial production surprised to the upside.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          23,
          44,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Salesforce raised its full-year revenue guidance to $38 billion, sending the stock up 3% in extended trading.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          10,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          52,
          63,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          86,
          88,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Saudi Arabia announced a voluntary production cut of 1 million barrels.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          35,
          49,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "HSBC appointed Georges Elhedery as its new Group Chief Financial Officer, effective January 1, 2023.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          4,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          15,
          31,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          43,
          72,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          84,
          99,
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Gary Gensler, the Chairman of the SEC, warned that 'AI-washing' in investment prospectuses would face strict enforcement actions.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "PER"
        ],
        [
          18,
          26,
          "ROLE"
        ],
        [
          34,
          37,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "While the S&P 500 rallied 1.2%, shares in Moderna slipped after the FDA delayed its review.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          10,
          17,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          26,
          30,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          42,
          49,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          68,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "China's producer price index (PPI) fell 2.7% year-on-year, signaling persistent deflationary pressure.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          5,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          8,
          34,
          "INDICATOR"
        ],
        [
          40,
          44,
          "PERCENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Saudi Arabia announced a voluntary production cut of 1 million barrels.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          12,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          35,
          49,
          "EVENT"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Macy's rejected a $5.8 billion buyout offer from Arkhouse Management and Brigade Capital.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          6,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          18,
          30,
          "MONEY"
        ],
        [
          49,
          68,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          73,
          88,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "The Department of Justice has opened a criminal probe into UnitedHealth regarding potential overcharging of the Medicare program.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          4,
          25,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          59,
          71,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          112,
          120,
          "ORG"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "Weekly jobless claims fell to 210,000, showing resilience.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          21,
          "INDICATOR"
        ]
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    "KKR acquired the remaining 37% stake in Global Atlantic for $2.7 billion.",
    {
      "entities": [
        [
          0,
          3,
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          27,
          30,
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          40,
          55,
          "ORG"
        ],
